Abdulrahman Salama

Junior FullStack php Dev.

Hello, My name is Abdulrahman. I'm 26 yr. I was born at Saudi Arabia "1993". Graduated from Modern Academy since 2015 with good degree. I worked in different fields. Started as a graphic designer for 1 year, Then as an Accountant for a half year. But finally i found myself choosing the childhood dream which is to become a Developer.



iabdorahman93@gmail.com

00201122166545

Cairo, Egypt **Q**

linkedin.com/in/iabdorahman93 in

github.com/iabdorahman 🦪

EDUCATION

High School the scientific track

2007 - 2010

Saudi Arabia

Management Information System Modern Academy

2011 - 2015

Egypt, Cairo

WORK EXPERIENCE

FreeLancer

Designer for T-shirts templates.

2017 - 2018

FullStack Dev. startup co. "Coinat.info".

2018

Accountant Lion Cub

2018 – 2019

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Einstein School - Admin panel. (10/2019)

 Private Project / please ask for permission. https://github.com/iabdorahman/einstein

CERTIFICATES

FullStack php. (03/2019 – 10/2019)

Senior Steps - https://www.facebook.com/seniorsteps.it/

Front-End dev. "1MAC". (11/2018)

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Z1B90H4A744FRZVIWH2kSaB8_oZgWaS/view?usp=sharing

Android Developer Track "1MAC". (08/2018)

https://drive.google.com/file/d/19fEr9n3c1JFjHi0zVhVYhOOi0XWLL_Xf/view?usp=sharing

LANGUAGES

Arabic English
Native or Bilingual Proficiency Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

FootBall Swimming Reading Coding

Technology's